http://www.zigzagdesign.co.uk/privacy.html

Zigzag Web Design Privacy PolicyPlease read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website ?When using our site, as appropriate, you may be choose to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to send your details to us as an enquiry or information request.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, Use Live Chat or enter information on our site, or to provide us with feedback on our products or services.How do we use your information? We may use the information we collect from you when you sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, browse the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:• To improve our website in order to better serve you.• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To ask for ratings and reviews of services• To follow up after correspondence (live chat, email or phone enquiries)How do we protect your information?We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.We use regular Malware Scanning.We do not use an SSL certificate - we only provide articles and information. We never ask for private information such as credit card numbers.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to:Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you turn cookies off, It won't affect the user experience .Third-party disclosureWe do not sell or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.GoogleGoogle's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enGoogle, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.We have implemented the following:• Google Display Network Impression ReportingWe, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:• On our Privacy Policy PageYou can change your personal information:• By emailing us : info@zigzagdesign.co.uk• By calling us : 01273 956977How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral trackingWe do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.CAN SPAM ActWe collect your email address in order to:• Send information, respond to enquiries, and/or other requests or questionsTo be in accordance with CANSPAM, for newsletter and marketing communications we agree to the following:• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.• Include the physical address of our business .• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence. Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.www.zigzagdesign.co.ukMaria House, 35 Millers RoadBrightonEast Sussex BN1 5NPUKinfo@zigzagdesign.co.uk01273 956977Last Edited on 23/04/2018
Web Design Custom Web Design Website Portfolio News & Articles Site MapEcommerce About E-commerce Client Portfolio Payment Providers ArticlesSEO Search Engine Optimisation SEO / Support Packages Customer TestimonialsOther Info Social Media Email Marketing Domain Name Registration Website Hosting FAQsContact Us Contact Info Enquiry Form Tel: 01273 956 977 E: info@zigzagdesign.co.uk
© 2020 Zigzag Web Design			All Rights Reserved Privacy Policy
Brighton Web Design, SEO & Ecommerce Agency     Tel: 01273 956 977
HOMEE-COMMERCESearch Engine OptimisationPORTFOLIOWeb DesignThe Other StuffWhat Our Customers Have to SayEmail MarketingSocial Media for BusinessEcommerce Payment ProvidersNews & ArticlesRegister Domain NamesWebsite HostingCONTACT US
